AoM Records 5289
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series SERIES I. ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
  - Sub-Series C. EXECUTIVE OFFICERS.
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 89)
      Annual Meeting, registrations
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 90)
      Annual Meeting, publisher relations
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 91)
      Annual Meeting, internal support services
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 8, Folder 92)
      Annual Meeting, Proceedings guidelines
    - Wortman, M. (Box 8, Folder 93)
      Annual meetings, public relations
    - Wortman, M., 1981 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Wortman, M., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 95)
      Annual Meeting, Presidential address
    - Wortman, M., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Wortman, M., 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 97)
      Annual Meeting, correspondence, 1982, includes 1984 Annual Meeting contracts for hotel and meeting room accommodations
    - Wortman, M., 1981-1985 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Wortman, M., 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Wortman, M., 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      official correspondence
    - Wortman, M., 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      committee assignments
    - Wortman, M., 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Wortman, M., 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      goals statement
    - Wortman, M., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Presidential Award
    - Wortman, M., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      letters of recommendation
    - Wortman, M., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      minority involvement in Academy, correspondence
    - Wortman, M., 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Wortman, M., 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Committee on Awards
    - Wortman, M., 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Membership Committee
    - Wortman, M., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Nominating Committee, election ballots and results
    - Wortman, M., 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Wortman, M., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Wortman, M., 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Wortman, M., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Wortman, M., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      Placement Committee
    - Wortman, M., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Wortman, M., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      Centennial Committee, correspondence
    - Wortman, M., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      Constitution and By-Laws Revision Committee
    - Wortman, M., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      Incorporation Committee
    - Wortman, M., 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Wortman, M., 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Wortman, M., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Wortman, M., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      Organizational Development Division, correspondence
    - Wortman, M., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      Organization and Management Theory Division, correspondence
    - Wortman, M., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Productions/Operations Management Division, correspondence
    - Wortman, M., 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      Careers Interest Group, correspondence, includes correspondence re: the group's creation
    - Wortman, M., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      Research & Development/Technology/ Innovation Interest Group, correspondence
    - Wortman, M., 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      Women in Management Interest Group, correspondence, includes correspondence re: the group's creation
    - Wortman, M., 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      American Assembly of Collegiate Schools of Business (AACSB)
    - Wortman, M., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      American Institute for Decision Sciences (AIDS), correspondence
    - Wortman, M., 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Wortman, M., 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Wortman, M., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      Academy of Management Newsletter, correspondence
    - Wortman, M., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      Publications, correspondence
    - Wortman, M., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      Publication advertising, correspondence
    - Wortman, M., 1968-1984 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series D. ACADEMY OF MANAGEMENT HISTORIANS RECORDS.
    This office maintains materials of significant value regarding the history of the Academy. As of the date of this processing, Charles D. Wrege has been the only person to hold this office. The records emphasize the history of management theory and the Management History Division.
    - Sub-Series 1. Subject Files, by year
      - Centennial Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 38)
        includes correspondence re: the Centennial of Modern Management, planned for 1986
      - Frederick W. Taylor Souvenir Booklet, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 39)
        material and correspondence
      - F.W. Taylor Souvenier Booklets, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Centennial Committee, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Management History Division, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - General Academy correspondence, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Hawthorne Symposium, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 44)
      - General Academy correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - Centennial Committee, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 46-47)
      - Research Conference on Management History, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - Management History Division, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 49)
      - Centennial Committee, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - Symposium: Hawthorne: Getting the Story Straight, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 51)
        proposal by Charles Wrege
      - Centennial Committee, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 52)
      - Management History Division, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 53-55)
      - Management History Division, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 56)
        Program
      - Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 57)
      - General correspondence, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 58)
      - Centennial Committee, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 59)
      - Centennial Committee, Oral History by Keith Davis, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 60)
      - Management History Division, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 61)
      - Management History Division, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 62)
      - The Business History Conference, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 63)
      - Symposium: The Path to Bethlehem, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 64)
        for the Eastern Academy of Management
      - General correspondence, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 65)
      - Centennial Committee, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 66)
      - Centennial Proceedings, plans, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 67)
      - Management History Division, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 68)
      - Management History Division, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 69)
      - General correspondence, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 70)
      - Centennial Commemorative Proceedings, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 71)
      - Centennial Committee, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 72)
      - Centennial, general correspondence, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 73)
      - A Question of Management: A Historical Perspective", 1986 (Box 9, Folder 74)
      - Centennial Proceedings, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 75)
      - Archives of the Academy of Management Display at 1986 Annual Meeting (Box 9, Folder 76)
        contains original documents re: the Academy's beginnings
      - Symposium on Creativity and Innovation in Management, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 1)
        Centennial Meeting
      - Symposium on Creativity and Innovation in Management, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 2)
        Centennial Meeting, correspondence
      - Calendar of Management Scholars Birthdays, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Management History Division, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Academy Officers, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - General correspondence, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Management History Division, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Eastern Academy of Management, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Academy of Management Review (AMR), 1987 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - General correspondence, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Video History Project, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Management History Division, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Fellows Group, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - General Academy correspondence, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Management History Division, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Wrege, C., Academy Historian, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 16)
        Report of the History
      - Historians Office, budget, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Fellows Group, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Symposium on Committee on Human Relations in Industry, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - General Academy correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - Management History Division, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Volunteer Committee, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - General Academy correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Citizen Ambassador Program of People to People International, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - Report of Academy Historian to the Board of Governors (BOG), 1993 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Historians Office, finances, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Report on Archives and Historians Activities to the BOG, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Sub-Series 2. Official History of the Academy of Management (Compiled by C.D. Wrege)
      - Copy of 3rd Annual Academy of Management Meeting Proceedings, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 29)
        12/30/1938
      - Reactivation of the Academy of Management, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - List of Past-Presidents, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - McKinsey Foundation Book Awards, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - Wrege, C., The Inception, Early Struggles, and Flowering of the Academy of Management, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 33)
        written for 1986 Centennial of Management
      - Manuscript, The Inception, Early Struggles (Box 10, Folder 34)
      - 1st Draft, The Inception, Early Struggles (Box 10, Folder 35)
      - 2nd Draft, The Inception, Early Struggles (Box 10, Folder 36)
      - George Gore, notes on The Inception, Early Struggles (Box 10, Folder 37)
      - Individuals Histories, correspondence, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      - Academy History, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 39)
        notes, 5/9/86
    - Sub-Series 3. Individuals Histories of the Academy of Management
      - Davis, K., History (Box 10, Folder 40)
      - Goetz, B., History (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - Gore, G., History (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - LeBreton, P. History (Box 10, Folder 43)
      - Mee, J., The First Ten Years of the Academy of Management (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Towle, J., History (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Sub-Series 4. Archives of the Academy of Management
      Correspondence regarding the establishment, functions, upkeep, and finances of the Archives; compiled by Charles Wrege.
      - Archives, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 48)
        includes a letter to the Board of Governors (BOG) re: the current state of the archives
      - Archives, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 49)
        guidelines, regulations, and information about the archives at Cornell University
      - Archives, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Archives, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Archives, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 52)
        includes a letter conferring the position of Academy Historian on Charles Wrege and charging him with developing the Archives
      - Archives, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 53)
        includes the memorandum of agreement between the Academy and the Labor-Management Documentation Center at Cornell University
      - Guide to the Archives, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      - Archives, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 55)
        includes updated guidelines for material acquisition
      - Archives, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 56)
      - Archives, 1984-1987 (Box 10, Folder 57)
      - Archives, oral history interview tips (Box 10, Folder 58)
      - Wrege, C. The Past, Present, and Future of the Academy of Management Archives, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 59)
      - Archives, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 60)
        includes 1988 and 1989 Archives report prepared by C. Wrege; history of the original Academy Archives
      - Archives, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 61)
        includes 1990 Historian's report, updated 1991 Guidelines for Donation of Materials; 1992 Archives budget
      - Archives, 1993-1995 (Box 10, Folder 62)
        Includes 1993 budget
  - Sub-Series E. COMMITTEE RECORDS.
    At the National level, the Academy of Management operates many committees, both standing and ad-hoc. This series encompasses all the material emanating from those committees. It is arranged in hierarchical order with All-Academy standing committees first, followed by All-Academy ad-hoc committees. See Academy Handbooks, box 4, file folders 1 6 for more information.
    - Sub-Series 1 All-Academy Standing Committees
      - Professional Division Policy Committee, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 63)
      - Professional Division Policy Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 64)
      - Professional Division Policy Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      - Professional Division Policy Committee, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 66)
      - Professional Division Policy Committee, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 67)
      - Professional Division Review Committee, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 68)
      - Professional Division Review Committee, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 69)
      - Professional Division Review Committee, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 70)
      - Professional Division Review Committee, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 71)
      - Professional Division Review Committee, Policy Statement, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 72)
      - Professional Division Review Committee, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 73)
      - Professional Division Review Committee, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 74)
      - Professional Division Review Committee, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 75)
      - Professional Division Review Committee, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 76)
      - Program Committee, 1940-1970 (Box 10, Folder 77)
        Includes the programs for annual meetings, announcements of the program, and calls for papers for the program
      - Program Committee, 1971-1979 (Box 10, Folder 78)
      - Program Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 79)
        Includes financial report for 1982 meeting and the beginnings of the formalized Call for Papers now used by the Academy
      - Program Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 10, Folder 80)
      - Program Committee, correspondence, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 81)
      - Program Committee, Call for Papers, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 82)
      - Program Committee, Call for Papers, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 83)
      - Program Committee, Call for Papers, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 84)
      - Committee on the Status of Women, 1976-1991 (Box 10, Folder 85)
        Includes the purpose and progress of the Committee in 1982; the proposal to create the Academy of Management Handbook in 1982
      - Finance Committee, 1950-1971 (Box 10, Folder 86)
        Includes correspondence re: the chairmanship and administrative arrangements
      - Budget Committee, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 87)
        Fiscal Year
      - Budget Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 88)
      - Budget Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 89)
      - Budget Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 90)
      - Budget Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 91)
      - Budget Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 92)
      - Budget Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 93)
      - Budget Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 94)
      - Budget Committee, 1991-1991 (Box 10, Folder 95)
      - Placement Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 96)
        Includes materials regarding the formation of the Committee in 1961
      - Placement Committee, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 97)
        rosters
      - Placement Committee, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Placement Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 99)
      - Placement Committee, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Placement Committee, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Placement Committee, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Placement Committee, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 103)
      - Placement Committee, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 104)
      - Placement Committee, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 105)
      - Placement Committee, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Placement Committee, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Placement Committee, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Placement Committee, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Placement Committee, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Placement Committee, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Placement Committee, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Placement Committee, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Placement Committee, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Placement Committee, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Placement Committee, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Placement Committee, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Placement Committee, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Placement Committee, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Placement Committee, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Placement Committee, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Placement Committee, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 17)
        roster, Fall 1983
      - Placement Committee, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Placement Committee, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 19)
        roster, Spring 1984
      - Placement Committee, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 20)
        roster, Fall 1984
      - Placement Committee, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Placement Committee, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 22)
        roster, Spring 1985
      - Placement Committee, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 23)
        roster, Fall 1985
      - Placement Committee, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Placement Committee, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 25)
        roster, Spring 1986
      - Placement Committee, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Placement Committee, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Placement Committee, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 28)
        roster, Spring 1987
      - Placement Committee, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 29)
        roster, Fall 1987
      - Placement Committee, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Placement Committee, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 31)
        roster, Spring 1988
      - Placement Committee, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 32)
        roster, Fall 1988
      - Placement Committee, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - Placement Committee, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 34)
        roster, Spring 1989
      - Placement Committee, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 35)
        roster, Fall 1989
      - Placement Committee, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Placement Committee, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 37)
        roster, Spring 1990
      - Placement Committee, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 38)
        roster, Fall 1990
      - Placement Committee, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - Placement Committee, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 40)
        roster, Spring 1991
      - Placement Committee, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 41)
        roster, Fall 1991
      - Placement Committee, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Placement Committee, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
        roster, Spring 1992
      - Placement Committee, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 3)
        roster, Fall 1992
      - Placement Committee, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Placement Committee, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 5)
        roster, Spring 1993
      - Placement Committee, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
        roster, Fall 1993
      - Placement Committee, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Placement Committee, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 8)
        roster, Spring 1994
      - Placement Committee, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 9)
        roster, Fall 1994
      - Placement Committee, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Placement Committee, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 11)
        roster, Spring 1995
      - Placement Committee, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Placement Committee, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 13)
        roster, Spring 1996
      - Placement Committee, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 14)
        roster, Fall 1996
      - Placement Committee, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Placement Committee, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 16)
        roster, Spring 1997
      - Placement Committee, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 17)
        roster, Fall 1997
      - Nominating Committee, 1949-1958 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Nominating Committee, 1962-1968 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Nominating Committee, 1970-1978 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Nominating Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Nominating Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Nominating Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - Nominating Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Nominating Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - Nominating Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - Nominating Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - Nominating Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - Nominating Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 29)
      - Nominating Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - Nominating Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 31)
      - Nominating Committee, list of Board of Governors (BOG) members, 1980-1990 (Box 12, Folder 32)
        list of nominees for Vice President and Program Chair, 1984 1990; list of nominees for BOG, 1984 1990; list of regional presidents, 1985 - 1990; list of Professional Division Chairpersons, 1985 - 1990; list of Regional Division officers, 1989 1990
      - Nominating Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - Nominating Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 34)
      - Nominating Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 35)
      - Nominating Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - Nominating Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - Nominating Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 38)
      - Nominating Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 39)
      - Membership Committee, 1947-1952 (Box 12, Folder 40)
        Includes membership rosters and nominations; 1949 action plan; general correspondence
      - Membership Committee, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 41)
        Includes materials of the Special Committee on Membership which addressed Academy growth
      - Membership Committee, 1954-1956 (Box 12, Folder 42)
        Includes general correspondence and membership applications
      - Membership Committee, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 43)
      - Membership Committee, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 44)
        BOG Report, April 1971
      - Membership Committee, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 45)
        Board of Governors (BOG) Report, August 1971
      - Membership Committee, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 46)
        BOG Report, December 1971
      - Membership Committee, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 47)
        promotions
      - Membership Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 48)
      - Membership Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 49)
      - Membership Committee, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 50)
        Includes 1980 Membership Survey, and results
      - Membership Committee, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 51)
      - Membership Committee, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 52)
      - Membership Committee, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 53)
        Includes 1987 Membership Survey
      - Membership Committee, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 54)
        Membership Survey, results
      - Membership Committee, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 55)
      - Membership Committee, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 56)
      - Membership Committee, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 57)
      - Membership Committee, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 58)
      - Membership Committee, 1956-1994 (Box 13, Folder 1)
        brochures
      - Membership Directory, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
        Oct-68
      - Membership Directory, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Membership Directory, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Membership Directory, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
        3 copies
      - Deleted (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Membership Directory, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Deleted (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Membership Directory, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 9)
        2 copies
      - Deleted (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Membership Directory, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Site Selection Committee, 1972-1979 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Site Selection Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Site Selection Procedures Manual, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Site Selection Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Site Selection Committee, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Outline of Activities for Local Arrangements Committee, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Site Selection Committee, 1987-1991 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Site Selection Committee, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 19)
        member survey